Amanda Steele Show. Today's goes to whichever court official allowed a Texas man who is running
for president to change his name to literally anybody else. He's doing this as basically like
a protest of sorts. He's actually a teacher. I find it hilarious and he is living out essentially
an article in The Onion. Today's letdown. This letdown goes to holy water and it's misuse
because it was splashed on New York Mayor Eric Adams. This weekend, Reverend Al Sharpton re-baptized
New York City Mayor Eric Adams as well as 11 detainees on Rikers Island as a sign that one
can be redeemed. Is this going to then change Eric Adams and the way that he is even dealing with
Rikers Island? What happens is these folks get in these positions and then they go on interviews as
politicians and people end up paying them a respect and reverence just because they're a politician
that completely undermines the necessity to have them show up and stand on the ways in which they
are affecting their constituency. You took the word out of my mouth because the royalty should have been
challenged as well but they are treated like they are divine and thus any decision they make is one
made by God and so they shouldn't be questioned and now that has passed down to these affected
officials. Actually affected officials. That was a Freudian slip.